Guide to the Salwa Mikdadi Papers AD.MC.022
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Artists files (individual), 1960-2005, and undated; 1989-1994; 12.5 Linear Feet in 30 boxes.
  - Elias, Hanna
    - Elias, Hanna, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Essa, Mervat
    - Essa, Mervat, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Essaadi, Mohamed
    - Essaadi, Mohamed, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Fakhro, Balqees
    - Fakhro, Balqees: biographical, 1990 and undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Fakhro, Balqees: correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Fakhro, Balqees: visuals, 1990-1992 and undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fakhoury, Bushra
    - Fakhoury, Bushra, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Farah, Rima
    - Farah, Rima: biographical, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Farah, Rima: correspondence, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Farah, Rima: visuals, 1987-1988 and undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Faraj, Maysaloun
    - Faraj, Maysaloun: biographical, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Faraj, Maysaloun: correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Faraj, Maysaloun: visuals, 1986-1988 and undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Farhat, Sofia
    - Farhat, Sofia, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Farra, Leila
    - Farra, Leila: biographical, 1976-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Farra, Leila: correspondence, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Farra, Leila: visuals, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Fattal, Simone
    - Fattal, Simone: biographical, 1990 and undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Fattal, Simone: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Fattal, Simone: visuals, 1977-1999 and undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fekaiki, Betool al-
    - Fekaiki, Betool al-, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Frenn, Chawky
    - Frenn, Chawky: biographical, 2001-2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Frenn, Chawky: correspondence, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Frenn, Chawky: visuals, 2001-2004 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Ftouni, Amal
    - Ftouni, Amal: biographical, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ftouni, Amal: correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ftouni, Amal: visuals, 1992 and undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gargour, Marianne
    - Gargour, Marianne, 1994 and undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gboubi, Fatima
    - Gboubi, Fatima, 1989 and undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Genoura, Salam
    - Genoura, Salam, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - George, Saadeh
    - George, Saadeh: biographical and correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - George, Saadeh: visuals, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ghaibeh, Lina
    - Ghaibeh, Lina: biographical, 1992-1993 and undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ghaibeh, Lina: correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ghaibeh, Lina: visuals, 1992 and undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ghaibeh, May
    - Ghaibeh, May, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ghani, Mariam
    - Ghani, Mariam, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Ghani, Mohammed
    - Ghani, Mohammed: correspondence and visuals, 1996 and undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Ghannam, Renata
    - Ghannam, Renata, 1970-1999 and undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Ghassib, Riham
    - Ghassib, Riham: biographical, 1992 and undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Ghassib, Riham: correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Ghassib, Riham: visuals, 1993 and undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ghoussoub, Mai
    - Ghoussoub, Mai, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Haddad, Lina
    - Haddad, Lina: biographical and correspondence, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Haddad, Lina: visuals, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Haddad, Najat
    - Haddad, Najat, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hadid, Zaha
    - Hadid, Zaha, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hakim, Elsi Huri
    - Hakim, Elsi Huri, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Halaby, Samia
    - Halaby, Samia: biographical, 1978-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Halaby, Samia: correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Halaby, Samia: visuals, 1981-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Halaka, John
    - Halaka, John: biographical, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Halaka, John: correspondence, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Halaka, John: visuals, 1988-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Halim, Taliha
    - Halim, Taliha, 1978 and undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hallaj, Mustafa al-
    - Hallaj, Mustafa al-, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hamak, Farida
    - Hamak, Farida, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Hammoud, Dana
    - Hammoud, Dana, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Handal, Alexandra
    - Handal, Alexandra, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Hassan, Fathi
    - Hassan, Fathi, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Hassan el-Farouj, Fatima
    - Hassan el-Farouj, Fatima: biographical, 1974-1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Hassan el-Farouj, Fatima: correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Hassan el-Farouj, Fatima: visuals, 1989-1994 and undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Hassan, Jamelie
    - Hassan, Jamelie: biographical, 1990-1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hassan, Jamelie: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hassan, Jamelie: visuals, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hatoum, Mona
    - Hatoum, Mona: biographical, 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Hatoum, Mona: correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hatoum, Mona: visuals, 1992 and undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Hazboun, Norma
    - Hazboun, Norma, 1987 and undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Henein, Adam
    - Henein, Adam, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hicheri, Fawzia el-
    - Hicheri, Fawzia el-: biographical, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hicheri, Fawzia el-: correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Hicheri, Fawzia el-: visuals, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hilal, Sandi
    - Hilal, Sandi, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hilmi, Nabila
    - Hilmi, Nabila: biographical, 1992-2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Hilmi, Nabila: correspondence, 1993-2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Hilmi, Nabila: visuals, 1989-2002 and undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hodeib, Hala Hilmi
    - Hodeib, Hala Hilmi: biographical, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Hodeib, Hala Hilmi: visuals, 1999 and undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Houdaybi, Wafaa el-
    - Houdaybi, Wafaa el-: biographical, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Houdaybi, Wafaa el-: correspondence, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Houdaybi, Wafaa el-: visuals, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Husseini, Fawzia
    - Husseini, Fawzia, 1987 and undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Husseini, Jumana el-
    - Husseini, Jumana el-: biographical, 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Husseini, Jumana el-: correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Husseini, Jumana el-: visuals, 1977-1991 and undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Husseini, Rose
    - Husseini, Rose, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ibrahim, Shalabiya
    - Ibrahim, Shalabiya, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Iguelmamene, Fatihe Kabeche
    - Iguelmamene, Fatihe Kabeche: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Iguelmamene, Fatihe Kabeche: visuals, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ikramullah, Naz
    - Ikramullah, Naz, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ishaq, Kamala
    - Ishaq, Kamala: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Ishaq, Kamala: visuals, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Izugarhan, Naima
    - Izugarhan, Naima, 1989 and undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Izzedin, Aida
    - Izzedin, Aida: biographical and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Izzedin, Aida: visuals, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Jaar, Siham Abu Acle
    - Jaar, Siham Abu Acle: biographical, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jaar, Siham Abu Acle: correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jaar, Siham Abu Acle: visuals, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Jacir, Emily
    - Jacir, Emily: biographical, 1994-2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jacir, Emily: correspondence, 1995-2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Jacir, Emliy: visuals, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Jamal, Ghadia
    - Jamal, Ghadia: biographical, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Jamal, Ghadia: correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Jamal, Ghadia: visuals, 1989-1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Junblat, Samia
    - Junblat, Samia, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kalache, Hiba
    - Kalache, Hiba: biographical, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Kalache, Hiba: visuals, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Kanafani, Fay Afaf
    - Kanafani, Fay Afaf, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Kandalaft, Juhaina
    - Kandalaft, Juhaina, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Kanso, Nabil
    - Kanso, Nabil, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Karnouk, Liliane
    - Karnouk, Liliane: biographical, 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Karnouk, Liliane: correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Karnouk, Liliane: visuals, 1985-1994 and undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kaspales, Farouk
    - Kaspales, Farouk, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Kassatly, Houda
    - Kassatly, Houda: biographical, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Kassatly, Houda: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Kassatly, Houda: visuals, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Kawash, Leila
    - Kawash, Leila: biographical, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Kawash, Leila: correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Kawash, Leila: visuals, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Kehdi, Noucetta
    - Kehdi, Noucetta, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Kelekian, Hilda and Lena
    - Kelekian, Hilda and Lena, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Khal, Helen
    - Khal, Helen: biographical, 1991-1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Khal, Helen: correspondence, 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Khal, Helen: visuals, 1986-1991 and undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Khalaf, Lamis
    - Khalaf, Lamis, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Khalil, Mohammed
    - Khalil, Mohammed: biographical and correspondence, 1992-2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Khalil, Mohammed: visuals, 2004 and undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Khalil, Zena el-
    - Khalil, Zena el-: biographical and visuals, 2004 and undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Khanfar, Yousef
    - Khanfar, Yousef, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Khemir, Sabiha
    - Khemir, Sabiha: biographical and correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Khemir, Sabiha: visuals, 1993 and undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Khoury, Sandra
    - Khoury, Sandra: biographical and correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Khoury, Sandra: visuals, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Knebel, Jane
    - Knebel, Jane: biographical and correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Knebel, Jane: visuals, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Koraichi, Rashid
    - Koraichi, Rashid: biographical, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Koraichi, Rashid: visuals, 1985-1995 and undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kuhl, Christopher
    - Kuhl, Christopher, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lababidi, Hala
    - Lababidi, Hala, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Long, Aida Antonios (Khalife)
    - Long, Aida Antonios (Khalife), 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Madkour, Nazli
    - Madkour, Nazli: biographical, 1992-2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Madkour, Nazli: correspondence, 1993-2004 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Madkour, Nazli: visuals, 1989-1990 and undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Mahieddine, Baya
    - Mahieddine, Baya: biographical, 1982-1983 and undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Mahieddine, Baya: correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Mahieddine, Baya: visuals, 1966-1976 and undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Mahmoud, Nadira
    - Mahmoud, Nadira: biographical and correspondence, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Mahmoud, Nadira: visuals, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Mahmoud, Rabha
    - Mahmoud, Rabha: biographical and correspondence, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Mahmoud, Rabha: visuals, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Majure, Ilham
    - Majure, Ilham: biographical, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Majure, Ilham: visuals, undated, circa 2002 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Makhoul, Bashir
    - Makhoul, Bashir: biographical and correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Makhoul, Bashir: visuals, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Manoukian, Seta
    - Manoukian, Seta: biographical, 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Manoukian, Seta: correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Manoukian, Seta: visuals, 1980-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mansour, Anita
    - Mansour, Anita, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mansour, Sliman
    - Mansour, Sliman: biographical, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Mansour, Sliman: visuals, 1975-1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Mardam Bey, Rima
    - Mardam Bey, Rima: biographical, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Mardam Bey, Rima: correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Mardam Bey, Rima: visuals, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Masri, Sana al-
    - Masri, Sana al-, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Meghelli, Fethi
    - Meghelli, Fethi, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mehadji, Najia
    - Mehadji, Najia: biographical, 1990-1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Mehadji, Najia: visuals, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Mezghani, Feriel
    - Mezghani, Feriel, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mezian, Miriam
    - Mezian, Miriam: biographical and correspondence, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Mezian, Miriam: visuals, 1994 and undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Millns, Patricia
    - Millns, Patricia: biographical and correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Millns, Patricia: visuals, 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Moghraby, Siham
    - Moghraby, Siham, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mokarem, Amal
    - Mokarem, Amal, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mosly, Mounirah Ahmad
    - Mosly, Mounirah Ahmad: biographical, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Mosly, Mounirah Ahmad: correspondence, 1992-2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Mosly, Mounirah Ahmad: visuals, 1985-1991 and undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Moudarres, Fateh
    - Moudarres, Fateh, 1976-1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mouhoubi, Akila
    - Mouhoubi, Akila, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mourabet, Ali el-
    - Mourabet, Ali el-: correspondence, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Mourabet, Ali el-: visuals, 1995-1998 and undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Mourad, Jumana
    - Mourad, Jumana, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Mufti, Dalal Haidari al-
    - Mufti, Dalal Haidari al-, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Muraywed, Amal
    - Muraywed, Amal, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Muraywid, Laila
    - Muraywid, Laila: biographical, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Muraywid, Laila: correspondence, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Muraywid, Laila: visuals, 1990-1993 and undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Mushriqui, Magdi Wadie
    - Mushriqui, Magdi Wadie: biographical, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Mushriqui, Magdi Wadie: visuals, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Mustafa, Maha
    - Mustafa, Maha, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Naamani, Hoda al-
    - Naamani, Hoda al-, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Nagui, Effat
    - Nagui, Effat: biographical and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Nagui, Effat: visuals, 1976-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Nahas, Nabil
    - Nahas, Nabil, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Nakhla, Marguerite
    - Nakhla, Marguerite, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Nami, Yolande
    - Nami, Yolande, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Nashashibi, Ibraham
    - Nashashibi, Ibraham: biographical, 1993 and undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Nashashibi, Ibraham: visuals, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Nashashibi, Rosalind
    - Nashashibi, Rosalind, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Nasiri, Rafa
    - Nasiri, Rafa, 1996-1997 and undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Nassar, Denise
    - Nassar, Denise, 1998-2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Nasser, Hind Mango
    - Nasser, Hind Mango: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Nasser, Hind Mango: visuals, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Nawash, Ahmed, 1981-1996, and undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Naufal, Yolande
    - Naufal, Yolande: biographical and correspondence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Naufal, Yolande: visuals, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Nazir, Reem Fuad
    - Nazir, Reem Fuad, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Nemr, Rabab
    - Nemr, Rabab: biographical, 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Nemr, Rabab: correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Nemr, Rabab: visuals, 1985 and undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Niati, Houria
    - Niati, Houria: biographical, 1984-1990 and undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Niati, Houria: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Niati, Houria: visuals, 1982-1983 and undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Nimer, Ayyad al-
    - Nimer, Ayyad al-: biographical and correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Nimer, Ayyad al-: visuals, 1988, and undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Noursi, Suha
    - Noursi, Suha: biographical, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Noursi, Suha: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Noursi, Suha: visuals, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Nseier, Leyla
    - Nseier, Leyla, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Nuseibeh, Said
    - Nuseibeh, Said: biographical, 1995-2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Nuseibeh, Said: correspondence:, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Nuseibeh, Said: visuals, 1989-1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Omar, Ekram
    - Omar, Ekram: biographical and correspondence, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Omar, Ekram: visuals, 1982-1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Omar, Iman
    - Omar, Iman: biographical and correspondence, 1992, and undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Omar, Iman, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Omary, Carmela
    - Omary, Carmella, 1991 and undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Othman, Souhair
    - Othman, Souhair, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Pashi, Marwan Qassab
    - Pashi, Marwan Qassab, 1970-1994 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Qasimi, Maysoon Saqr al-
    - Qasimi, Maysoon Saqr al-: biographical, 1993 and undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Qasimi, Maysoon Saqr al-: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Qasimi, Maysoon Saqr al-: visuals, 1992-1993 and undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Qassib, Khalid al-
    - Qassib, Khalid al-, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Qotbi, Mehdi
    - Qotbi, Mehdi: correspondence, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Qotbi, Mehdi: visuals, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Raad, Nada, 1987-1993
    - Raad, Nada: biographical and correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Raad, Nada: visuals, 1987-1990 and undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ra'ad, Walid, 2002-2003
    - Ra'ad, Walid, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rabah, Khalil, 1995-1996
    - Rabah, Khalil, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Radi, Nuha al-
    - Radi, Nuha al-: biographical, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Radi, Nuha al-: visuals, 1990 and undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Rahou Robichet, Fatiha
    - Rahou Robichet, Fatiha: biographical, 1980-1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Rahou Robichet, Fatiha: visuals, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Raissouni, Kenza
    - Raissouni, Kenza: biographical and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Raissouni, Kenza: visuals, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Raoui, Salima
    - Raoui, Salima, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rashid, Naziha
    - Rashid, Naziha: biographical and correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Rashid, Naziha: visuals, 1985-1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Rawas, Mohamed
    - Rawas, Mohamed, 1990-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Reda, Fawzia
    - Reda, Fawzia: biographical and correspondence, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Reda, Fawzia: visuals, 1997-2002 and undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Ringwald, Lydia
    - Ringwald, Lydia: biographical, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ringwald, Lydia: correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ringwald, Lydia: visuals, 1988-1992 and undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Rizk, Ufemia
    - Rizk, Ufemia: biographical and correspondence, 1977-1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Rizk, Ufemia: visuals, 1993 and undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Saadeh, Raeda
    - Saadeh, Raeda, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sabagh, Wafa
    - Sabagh, Wafa, 1997 and undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sabbagh, Sana
    - Sabbagh, Sana, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sabella, Steve
    - Sabella, Steve, 2004-2008 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sadoun, Mohamed al-
    - Sadoun, Mohamed al-: biographical, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sadoun, Mohamed al-: correspondence, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Sadoun, Mohamed al-: visuals, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Safey al-Din, Yassar
    - Safey al-Din, Yassar, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sakkal, Mamoun
    - Sakkal, Mamoun: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sakkal, Mamoun: visuals, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Salam, Rana
    - Salam, Rana: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Salam, Rana: visuals, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Saleh, Khairat al-
    - Saleh, Khairat al-: biographical, 1989-2000 (Box 22, Case 9)
    - Saleh, Khairat al-: correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 22, Case 10)
    - Saleh, Khairat al-: visuals, 1995 and undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Salem, Zeinab
    - Salem, Zeinab, 1986-1992 and undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Salloum, Jackie
    - Salloum, Jackie, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Samaha, Sumayyah
    - Samaha, Sumayyah: biographical and correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Samaha, Sumayyah: visuals, 1990-2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sarabat, Jan (collector)
    - Sarabat, Jan (collector), Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Saudi, Mona
    - Saudi, Mona: biographical, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Saudi, Mona: correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Saudi, Mona: visuals, 1992-1996 and undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Sawalhi, Salwa al-
    - Sawalhi, Salwa al-: biographical, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sawalhi, Salwa al-: visuals, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sawaya, Linda
    - Sawaya, Linda: biographical and correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Sawaya, Linda: visuals, 1986-1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sayagh, Jumana
    - Sayagh, Jumana: biographical and correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Sayagh, Jumana: visuals, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Sayyid, Sitt
    - Sayyid, Sitt, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Sedjal, Azdine
    - Sedjal, Azdine, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Sehnaoui, Mouna Bassili
    - Sehnaoui, Mouna Bassili: biographical, 1987-1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Sehnaoui, Mouna Bassili: correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Sehnaoui, Mouna Bassili: visuals, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Selim, Neziha
    - Selim, Neziha, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Seraphime, Juliana
    - Seraphime, Juliana, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Schoukair, Hala
    - Schoukair, Hala: biographical and correspondence, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Schoukair, Hala: visuals, 1984-1992 and undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Shabout, Nada
    - Shabout, Nada, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Shafik, Medhat
    - Shafik, Medhat, 2005 and undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Shakir, Muhammed Ali
    - Shakir, Muhammed Ali, 1997 and undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Shammout, Ismail
    - Shammout, Ismail, 1990-1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Shammout, Ismail: draft of book, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Shamounki, Diana
    - Shamounki, Diana: Biographical, 1986 and undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Shamounki, Diana: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Shamounki, Diana: Visuals, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Shawa, Leila
    - Shawa, Leila: biographical, 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Shawa, Leila: correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Shawa, Leila: visuals, 1990-1994, and undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Shayota, Athir
    - Shayota, Athir: biographical, 1993-1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Shayota, Athir: correspondence, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Shayota, Athir: visuals, 1987-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Shenasa, Nazanin
    - Shenasa, Nazanin, 1996-2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Shishiny, Naima el-
    - Shishiny, Naima el-: Biographical and correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)